[
  {
    "id": 1,
    "title": "Quiz 1",
    "questions": [
      {
        "correctAnswer": "The Moon",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["The Sun", "Halley's Comet", "Mars"],
        "question": "What celestial object was the first for humankind to set foot on?"
      },
      {
        "correctAnswer": "Queen Victoria",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["Queen Elizabeth II", "Queen Mary", "Queen Anne"],
        "question": "Which British queen did not go out in public for three years after the death of her husband in 1861?"
      },
      {
        "correctAnswer": "Haruki Murakami",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["Oscar Wilde", "Umberto Eco", "SÃ¸ren Kierkegaard"],
        "question": "Which author wrote 'The Elephant Vanishes'?"
      },
      {
        "correctAnswer": "A mother personally challenges the local authorities to solve her daughter's murder.",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "The drug-induced utopias of four addicts are shattered when their addictions run deep.",
          "A paleontologist is tasked with protecting two children when cloned dinosaurs are set free.",
          "A destitute family builds a symbiotic relationship with a wealthy family."
        ],
        "question": "What is the plot of the movie Three Billboards Outside Ebbing, Missouri?"
      },
      {
        "correctAnswer": "Mariah Carey",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["Rihanna", "Beyonce", "Christina Aguilera"],
        "question": "With Whom Did Boyz 2 Men Record The Single \"One Sweet Day\" In 1995\""
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "title": "Quiz 2",
    "questions": [
      {
        "correctAnswer": "Green",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["Nine", "Red", "Six"],
        "question": "In French, what is the meaning of the word 'vert'?"
      },
      {
        "correctAnswer": "California ",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["Florida", "Texas", "Kansas"],
        "question": "Which US state exports the most wine?"
      },
      {
        "correctAnswer": "Grog ",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["Guppy", "Roller", "Meal"],
        "question": "What was the name of the highly diluted rum that was once given to British sailors?"
      },
      {
        "correctAnswer": "Virginia Woolf",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["Oscar Wilde", "George Orwell", "Joseph Conrad"],
        "question": "Which author wrote 'Mrs Dalloway'?"
      },
      {
        "correctAnswer": "The Blues",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["The Hoops", "The Citizens", "Cottagers"],
        "question": "What is the nickname of the English football team Birmingham City?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "title": "Quiz 3",
    "questions": [
      {
        "correctAnswer": "Cincinnati Reds",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "Cincinnati Packers",
          "Cincinnati Real",
          "Cincinnati Suns"
        ],
        "question": "Which of these is a baseball team based in Cincinnati?"
      },
      {
        "correctAnswer": "Alpha & Omega",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["Beta & Gamma", "Sigma & Tau", "Delta & Epsilon"],
        "question": "What are the first and last letters of the Greek alphabet?"
      },
      {
        "correctAnswer": "A French cuff",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "A button cuff",
          "A barrel cuff",
          "A saville cuff"
        ],
        "question": "What is a wide cuff that is folded back and fastened with a cuff link called?"
      },
      {
        "correctAnswer": "Van Morrison ",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["Megadeth", "Boyz II Men", "Janet Jackson"],
        "question": "Who released the album 'Tupelo honey'?"
      },
      {
        "correctAnswer": "Eight",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["Four", "Twelve", "Sixteen"],
        "question": "How Many Lanes Does An Olympic Standard Swimming Pool Have?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "title": "Quiz 4",
    "questions": [
      {
        "correctAnswer": "George Harrison",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["John Lennon", "Paul McCartney", "Ringo Starr"],
        "question": "Who was the first Beatle to have a solo No 1 hit?"
      },
      {
        "correctAnswer": "Mozambique",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "Burkina Faso",
          "Sao Tome and Principe",
          "Micronesia"
        ],
        "question": "Maputo is the capital city of which country?"
      },
      {
        "correctAnswer": "Zoanthropy",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["Bobsy-die", "Agastopia", "Halfpace"],
        "question": "Which word is defined as 'delusion of a person who believes himself changed into an animal'?"
      },
      {
        "correctAnswer": "The Electoral College",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "The Supreme Court",
          "The Congress",
          "The House of Representatives"
        ],
        "question": "Which US government body is responsible for appointing the President and Vice President?"
      },
      {
        "correctAnswer": "Jules Verne",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "Victor Hugo",
          "Alphonse Daudet",
          "Edgar Rice Burroughs"
        ],
        "question": "Which author wrote 'From the Earth to the Moon'?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "title": "Quiz 5",
    "questions": [
      {
        "correctAnswer": "Houston Astros",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "Houston Predators",
          "Houston City",
          "Houston Football"
        ],
        "question": "Which of these is a baseball team based in Houston?"
      },
      {
        "correctAnswer": "The Middle East",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["India", "Central America", "Africa"],
        "question": "Where in the world are figs originally from?"
      },
      {
        "correctAnswer": "Halfpace",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["Yarborough", "Erf", "Bobsy-die"],
        "question": "Which word is defined as 'a platform of a staircase where the stair turns back in exactly the reverse direction of the lower flight'?"
      },
      {
        "correctAnswer": "The Boardwalk",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["The Beach", "The Pier", "The Promenade"],
        "question": "In the hit song sung by The Drifters, where are they \"on a blanket with my baby\"?"
      },
      {
        "correctAnswer": "Apple",
        "incorrectAnswers": ["Grape", "Plum", "Banana"],
        "question": "James Grieve and Egremont Russet are types of which fruit?"
      }
    ]
  }
]
